overwolf.com 2019-09-05

# Overwolf Privacy policy | Overwolf

### Terms of use

#### OVERWOLF TERMS OF SERVICE

Overwolf provides an in-game toolset, allowing applications to be displayed as an overlay above the graphic representation of a computer game using software ("Software") available for download at the Overwolf website located at www.overwolf.com (the "Site") together with documentation files accompanying the Software ("Documentation"). For purposes of these Terms of Service (the "Terms"), "Overwolf" shall include Overwolf Ltd., and its divisions, subsidiaries, successors, parent companies, if any, and their employees, partners, principals, agents and representatives, and any blogs, forums, sources of information or data available on the Site or Software. 

Please read the Terms carefully. These Terms govern your access to and use of the Site, including any information or data made available through the Site, any IM, VOIP, Video or chat services, or any blogs or forums available on the Site, as well as your downloading, installing or activating any Software and/or Documentation. The Site, Software and/or Documentation, information or data made available through the Site, any IM, VOIP, Video or chat services, or any blogs or forums available on the Site shall be collectively termed the "Services". 

This is a legal agreement between you and Overwolf. By accessing the Site or using the Services or downloading, installing or activating the Software or by clicking "I agree" below, you agree to be bound by these Terms, whether you are a "Visitor" (which means that you are only browsing the Site) or you are a "Member" (which means that you have registered with the Site or downloaded, installed or activated the Software). The term "User" refers to a Visitor or a Member. Your use of the Site and any Services, as well as any account you may have with Overwolf, is subject at all times to the Overwolf Terms (whether as a Visitor or a Member, regardless of whether your access or use is intended). Issues concerning collection and use of information by Overwolf are described in Overwolf Privacy Policy, which is incorporated herein. 

The Overwolf Site and Services are always evolving, so it is important that you periodically check here, as well as the specific rules for any Services in which you choose to participate, for updates. If we revise the Terms, such revision will take effect immediately upon being posted on the Site. By accessing the Site, or taking part in or downloading any Services, you agree to review the Terms periodically to become aware of such revisions. If you do not agree to any of the Terms stated herein, you should discontinue using the Site or participating in or using any Services. Overwolf reserves the right, in its sole discretion, at any time to modify, discontinue or terminate the Site and any Services without notice. Overwolf may also impose limits on certain features or restrict your access to or use of the Service, Site, or parts thereof in its sole discretion and without notice. 

Overwolf grants you a limited license to access and use the Site and Services subject to the terms and conditions of these Terms for your personal, non-commercial use and not for the benefit of any other person or entity. Overwolf grants you a non-exclusive license to use the Software, including any Documentation only in connection with a single discrete computer. This license does not allow you to make any commercial use or any derivative use of the Site or the Services (including any of its individual elements or Content (as defined below). All copyright notices must be retained at all times. You acknowledge that Overwolf may, at its sole discretion and at any time, discontinue providing any part of the Site or the Services without notice. 

You have no ownership rights in the Software. Rather, you have a license to use the Software as long as these Terms remain in full force and effect. Ownership of the Software, Documentation and all intellectual property rights therein shall remain at all times with Overwolf or its licensors. Any other use of the Software or Documentation by any person, business, corporation, government organization or any other entity is strictly forbidden and is a violation of these Terms. 

These Terms are your proof of license to exercise the rights granted herein and must be retained by you. You must protect the Software and Documentation consistent with Overwolf's rights therein, including informing persons who are permitted access thereto in order to satisfy your obligations hereunder and maintain the confidentiality of the Software and Documentation. 

Use of the Services and access to the Site is void where prohibited. By using the Site or Services, you represent and warrant that (a) all registration information you submit is truthful and accurate; (b) you will maintain the accuracy of such information; (c) you are 18 years of age or older or else, have your parent's or guardian's permission to enter into these Terms, or otherwise have the ability to form a binding contract; and (d) your use of the Services and/or Site does not violate any applicable law or regulation or any obligation you may have to a third party. 

You are welcome to link to the Site from your website, provided that your website does not imply any endorsement by or association with Overwolf. 

## PROPERTY

Overwolf owns the Site and Services, including all worldwide intellectual property rights in the Site, and Services, and the trademarks, service marks, and logos contained therein. Overwolf hereby grants you a limited, revocable, non sublicensable license to use the Site and Services solely for your personal use. Except as expressly permitted herein, you may not copy, further develop, reproduce, republish, modify, alter download, post, broadcast, transmit or otherwise use the Site or the Services. All rights not granted to you herein are reserved to Overwolf. You will not remove, alter or conceal any copyright, trademark, service mark or other proprietary rights notices incorporated in the Site, Content or Services. 

Certain types of content may be made available through the Site or Services. "Content" as used in these Terms means, collectively, all content on or made available through the Site or Services, including but not limited to information on any videos, blogs or forums available on the Site or Services. Overwolf reserves the rights to remove and permanently delete any Content from the Site or Services without notice. 

The Site and Services may contain blogs, forums, chat services (including IM, Video or VOIP services) to which Overwolf may allow you, in its sole discretion, to post Content. By submitting or posting such Content, you grant Overwolf and its successors a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, sub licensable and transferable license to use, copy, distribute, transmit, modify, prepare derivative works of, publicly display, and publicly perform such Content on, through or in connection with the Site or Services in any media formats and through any media channels, including without limitation, for commercially promoting the Site and Services. You are fully and solely responsible for anything you submit or post to the Site and/or Services, and represent and warrant that such Content complies with all applicable law and does not infringe third party intellectual property rights. Such posted or submitted Content shall not be considered confidential and may be disseminated by Overwolf without any compensation to you. This provision shall not apply to personal information that is subject to Overwolf's privacy policy except to the extent that you make such personal information publicly available on or through the Site or the Services. 

Under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (the "DMCA"), it is our policy to respond expeditiously to copyright owners who believe material appearing on the Site and/or Services infringes their rights. If you believe that something appearing on the Site and/or Services infringes your copyright, you may send us a notice requesting that it be removed, or access to it blocked. If you believe that such a notice has been wrongly filed against you, the DMCA lets you send us a counter-notice. Notices and counter-notices must meet the DMCA's requirements. We suggest that you consult your legal advisor before filing a notice or counter-notice. Be aware that there can be substantial penalties for false claims. Send notices and counter-notices to our support team: [support@overwolf.com](mailto:support@overwolf.com). 

Overwolf may provide you with the opportunity to download its logos, service marks and trademarks (together, the " **Marks** ") through the Site or Services. All Marks are the property of Overwolf and constitute important and valuable assets. All download and use of Marks are subject to the terms and conditions set forth herein. You may not use any Marks except as expressly set forth herein. 

You may refer to Overwolf products and services by their associated Marks, so long as such references (a) are truthful, fair, and not misleading, and (b) comply with these Terms. You may not incorporate Marks into your own product names, service names, applications, products, trademarks, logos or company names, and you may not adopt marks or logos that are confusingly similar to the Marks. You may not alter the Marks in any way or use them to refer to goods or services for which they were not originally intended. You may not use Marks on or in connection with any defamatory, scandalous, pornographic, or other objectionable materials of any sort, or in connection with any material that violates any applicable law, rule or regulation. 

You must use all trademarks, tradenames and service marks as adjectives to refer to the Overwolf products. You may not use any of the foregoing as nouns or verbs, pluralize them or make them a possessive. You may not join any of the foregoing to other words, symbols, or numbers, either as one word or with a hyphen. 

A Mark should be followed by a notice that it is being used as a trademark whenever possible. The trademark superscript symbol is preferred, but if it is not available, use parentheses such as, for example: (TM).ACCOUNT REGISTRATION 

## ACCOUNT REGISTRATION

You may need to register to use certain functionality of the Site and in order to download, install or activate the Software. When you complete the registration process, you create an Overwolf account and become a Member. Your account allows you to participate in certain Services, subject to the Terms and the Overwolf Privacy Policy, which is available at Privacy policy. Overwolf reserves the right to refuse to allow a User to open an account for any reason, or to limit the number of accounts a User can establish on the Site or with respect to the Services, all at Overwolf's sole discretion. 

To create an account, you must select a username and password. Your username is your Overwolf identity. You may not select a username that is used by someone else, and your username cannot be indecent, or otherwise offensive, or be used in any way that violates these Terms and common practices. You may not provide false information during the registration process. You must provide truthful and accurate information while creating your Overwolf account. 

You should not reveal your password to other users. Overwolf will not ask you to reveal your password. If you forget your password, you can request to have a new password sent to your registered e-mail address. Your account is at risk if you let someone use it inappropriately and your account is subject to termination if you or anyone using your account violates Overwolf Terms. If your account is terminated, you may not join Overwolf again without its express permission. 

You agree to immediately notify Overwolf of any unauthorized use of your Overwolf account or password. You are fully and solely responsible for the security of your computer system and all activity on your account, even if such activities were not committed by you. Overwolf will not be liable for any losses or damage arising from unauthorized use of your account or password, and you agree to indemnify and hold Overwolf harmless for any improper or illegal use of your account. This includes illegal or improper use by someone to whom you have given permission to use your account. 

## TERMINATION OF ACCOUNTS

You agree that Overwolf may for any reason, at its sole discretion and without notice, terminate your account, and remove from the Site or Services any Content associated with your account. Grounds for such termination may include but shall not be limited to (i) extended periods of inactivity, (ii) violation of the letter or spirit of these Terms, (iii) fraudulent, harassing or abusive behavior or (iv) behavior that is harmful to other users, third parties, or the business interests of Overwolf. 

If Overwolf believes, at its sole discretion, that a violation of these Terms or any illegal or inappropriate behavior has occurred, we may take any other corrective action we deem appropriate. We reserve the right to investigate suspected violations of these Terms or illegal and inappropriate behavior on the Site and/or Services. We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity of anyone believed to have violated these Terms or to have engaged in illegal behavior on the Site and/or Services. You may request termination of your Overwolf account at any time and for any reason by sending an email to [support@overwolf.com](mailto:support@overwolf.com). Any suspension, termination, or cancellation shall not affect your obligations to Overwolf under these Terms (including but not limited to ownership, indemnification, and limitation of liability), which by their sense and context are intended to survive such suspension, termination, or cancellation. 

## PAYMENTS

Some Services are provided free of charge. In some cases, we allow Members to pay for a monthly subscription (in the amount as determined by the app developer) in order to remove the advertisements from the Software/apps which they have downloaded. This is one way which Members can show support for the applicable app developer. When a Member signs up for a subscription, we will automatically charge him/her the applicable payment every month. The subscription months will be calculated from the date of payment. The Member may cancel the subscription at any time, such that s/he will continue to receive the benefits in connection with the subscription until the end of that month and his/her subscription will end at the end of that month. We reserve the right to modify, terminate or otherwise amend our offered subscription plans at any time in accordance with these Terms. We may change the price for the subscriptions, including recurring subscription fees from time to time and will communicate any price changes to you in advance and, if applicable, how to accept those changes. Price changes will take effect at the start of the next subscription period following the date of the price change. Subject to applicable law, you accept the new price by continuing to use the Service after the price change takes effect. If you do not agree with a price change, you have the right to reject the change by unsubscribing from the subscription prior to the price change going into effect. 

Overwolf currently accepts payments through PayPal, but may add or change payment methods in its sole discretion. You must respect the terms and conditions of any payment methods you use. We reserve the right to cancel any Services ordered if full payment is not timely received. We reserve the right to cancel any transaction that we have reason to believe to have been fraudulently made, including by unauthorized use of a credit card, debit card, or other payment method. 

You are solely responsible for any taxes on amounts you may pay or obtain through the Services. Overwolf will deduct applicable charges and taxes from any payable amounts, as required by law. 

## DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY

Your use of the Site, Content and Services is at your sole discretion and risk. The Site, Content and Services are provided on an AS IS and AS AVAILABLE basis without warranties of any kind from Overwolf. Some of the Content on the Site and/or Services shall be provided by third parties, including users of the Site and/or Services and Overwolf shall have no liability for such Content. OVERWOLF EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, RELATING TO THE SITE, CONTENT, AND SERVICES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF PROPRIETARY RIGHTS, COURSE OF DEALING OR COURSE OF PERFORMANCE. OVERWOLF DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED,: (I) REGARDING THE SECURITY, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY OF THE SITE, CONTENT, AND SERVICES; OR (II) THAT THE SITE AND SERVICES WILL BE ERROR-FREE OR THAT ANY ERRORS WILL BE CORRECTED; OR (III) REGARDING THE ACCURACY, QUALITY, CURRENCY, COMPLETENESS OR USEFULNESS OF ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED BY THE SITE AND SERVICES. Overwolf does not warrant that the functions contained in the Software will meet any requirements or needs you may have or that the Software is compatible with any particular platform. Overwolf is not obligated to provide any updates to the Software. Some jurisdictions do not allow the waiver or exclusion of implied warranties. Overwolf is not responsible for any incorrect or inaccurate Content posted on the Site or in connection with the Services, whether caused by Users of the Site or Services or by any of the equipment or programming associated with or utilized in the Site or Services. Overwolf takes no responsibility for third party advertisements which are posted on this Site or through the Services, nor does it take any responsibility for the goods or services provided by its advertisers. No advice or information, whether oral or written, obtained by you from Overwolf, shall create any warranty not expressly stated in these Terms. If you choose to rely on such information, you do so solely at your own risk. Some states or jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties. Accordingly, some of the above exclusions may not apply to you. 

## LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

IN NO EVENT SHALL OVERWOLF OR ANY OF ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR TO ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS, LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION) ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, CONTENT OR SERVICES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE QUALITY, ACCURACY, OR UTILITY OF THE INFORMATION PROVIDED. THE FOREGOING LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW IN THE APPLICABLE JURISDICTION AND IN NO EVENT SHALL OVERWOLF'S CUMULATIVE LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY AND ALL CLAIMS EXCEED U.S. $100. BECAUSE SOME STATES/COUNTRIES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. Overwolf is not responsible for any problems or technical malfunction of any telephone network or lines, computer online systems, servers or providers, computer equipment, software, failure of any email due to technical problems or traffic congestion on the internet, including any injury or damage to users or to any person's computer related to or resulting from participation or downloading materials in connection with the Software or Services. Under no circumstances shall Overwolf be responsible for any loss or damage resulting from use of the Site or Services from any content posted on or through the Site or Services or from the conduct of any users of the Site or Services. 

The Site, Services or Content may provide links to third-party websites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that Overwolf is not responsible or liable for the availability or accuracy of such websites or resources or the content, products, or services on or available from such websites or resources. You further acknowledge that Overwolf does not endorse such websites or resources or the content, products, or services on or available from such websites or resources. You acknowledge sole responsibility for and assume all risk arising from your use of any such websites or resources. 

You agree you will not do any of the following while using or accessing the Site, Services or any Content thereon: 

  1. Use the Site, Content, or Services in connection with any commercial endeavors in any manner, except for the purposes specifically set forth in these Terms; 
  2. Circumvent, disable, or otherwise interfere with security-related features of the Services or the Site or features that prevent or restrict use or copying of any Content; 
  3. Interfere with or disrupt (or attempt to interfere with or disrupt) any web page available at the Site and/or Services, servers, or networks connected to the Site and/or Services, or the technical delivery systems of Overwolf's providers, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies, or regulations of networks connected to the Site and/or Services; 
  4. Attempt to probe, scan, or test the vulnerability of any Overwolf system or network or breach or impair or circumvent any security or authentication measures protecting the Site and/or Services; 
  5. Publish, display, disclose, rent, lease, modify, copy, loan, distribute, or create derivative works based on the Site, Services, Content or any part thereof; 
  6. Attempt to decipher, decompile, disassemble, or reverse-engineer any of the software used to provide the Services or the Site; 
  7. Attempt to access, scrape, data mine, aggregate any data, search, or meta-search the Site, Services or Content thereon with any engine, software, tool, agent, device, or mechanism other than software and/or search agents provided by Overwolf or other generally available third-party web browsers, including without limitation any software that sends queries to the Site and/or Services to determine how a website or web page ranks; 
  8. Violate the Terms or any other rule or agreement applicable to you or Overwolf through the Site's and/or Services' inclusion in, reference to, or relationship with any third party or third-party site or service, or your use of any such third-party site or service; 
  9. Use, launch, or permit to be used any automated system, including without limitation "robots," "crawlers," or "spiders"; 
  10. Attempt to create the source code from the object code for the Software; 
  11. Transmit the Software over any network or between any devices; 
  12. Sublicense or permit use of the Software by more than one user; 
  13. Export the Software; or 
  14. Use the Site, Services or Content thereon in any manner not permitted by these Terms or in violation of applicable laws and regulations.

You have no ownership rights in the Software. Rather, you have a license to use the Software as long as these Terms remain in full force and effect. Ownership of the Software, Documentation and all intellectual property rights therein shall remain at all times with Overwolf or its licensors. Any other use of the Software or Documentation by any person, business, corporation, government organization or any other entity is strictly forbidden and is a violation of these Terms. 

These Terms are your proof of license to exercise the rights granted herein and must be retained by you. You must protect the Software and Documentation consistent with Overwolf's rights therein, including informing persons who are permitted access thereto in order to satisfy your obligations hereunder and maintain the confidentiality of the Software and Documentation. 

You agree to defend and indemnify Overwolf and its officers, directors, employees, and agents and to hold them harmless from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses, and expenses, including without limitation reasonable attorney's fees and costs, arising out of or in any way connected with (i) your access to or use of the Site and/or Services; or (ii) your violation of any of these Terms. 

The Overwolf client may include certain software made available under open source licenses (the "Open Source Software"). A list of such Open Source Software is available in Overwolf's installation folder under "Licenses". To the extent required by the applicable open source licenses, the terms and conditions of such licenses shall apply to the Open Source Software in lieu of the terms and conditions of these Terms. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in these Terms, Overwolf makes no warranties in respect of Open Source Software in excess of the warranties set forth in the applicable open source license itself, and accepts no liability in respect of Open Source Software in excess of the limitation of liability set forth in the applicable open source license. If any license requires Overwolf to provide source code, Overwolf shall make such source code available to you upon your written request according to the terms of the applicable open source license. 

In the event that any provision in these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable, the remaining provisions will remain in full force and effect. The failure of a party to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be deemed a waiver of such right or provision. Overwolf may assign these Terms or any rights hereunder without your consent. These Terms shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of Israel excluding that body of law pertaining to conflict of laws. Any legal action or proceeding arising under these Terms will be brought exclusively in courts located in Israel and the parties hereby irrevocably consent to the personal jurisdiction and venue therein. You agree that these Terms and the rules, restrictions, and policies contained herein, and Overwolf's enforcement thereof, are not intended to confer and do not confer any rights or remedies on any person other than you and Overwolf. 

_Last updated: August 2019_

### Privacy

#### OVERWOLF PRIVACY NOTICE

Overwolf respects your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the uses of your information is important to us. This Privacy Notice explains Overwolf's policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of Personal Data. The terms of this Privacy Notice apply to information collected by Overwolf from you, unless different terms are specified as part of a special offer or in another form or contract we provide you.

Overwolf products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties, for example, apps ("Third Party Apps") that are developed for the Overwolf platform by third parties ("Third Party App Developers"). Information collected by third parties, including by means of Third Party Apps, is governed by their privacy practices. By downloading any Third Party Apps you expressly agree to such privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

If not specifically defined herein, capitalized terms have the meaning given to them in the Overwolf Terms of Use, which is available at Terms of Use.

Under the applicable laws, Overwolf is the "data controller" of personal data collected through the Services.Our registered office is 19 Hayetzira St. Ramat Gan 5252157 and our registration number is 514330331. Sometimes we have access to the end user information on behalf of the Third Party Apps and/or Third Party App Developers. In such cases, the applicable Third Party App Developers serves as a controller with respect to such Third Party App Developer's end user Personal Data (as defined below).

" **Personal Data** " means any information that refers, is related to, or is associated with an identified or identifiable individual or as otherwise may be defined by applicable law.

## Privacy Notice Key Points 

The key points listed below are presented in further detail throughout this Privacy Notice. These key points do not substitute the full Privacy Notice.

  * **Personal Data We Collect.** When you download our client and/or register, we collect Personal Data provided by you, such as your username, email address and profile picture. If you register through a third party log-in/ account registration service (such as Facebook, Gmail, etc.), we collect your basic profile information from such third-party log-in/account registration service and your profile picture. We also collect Personal Data when you use the Services, such as games you played, language preference, referring site, pages viewed and the order of those pages etc, or contact us with questions or complaints. When you visit our Site and/or use the Services, we automatically collect your IP address, operating system, connected device, hardware details and other information about your use of the Site and/or Services. We can receive aggregated data containing impressions, revenue, video stats, as well as confirmation of user completions. 
  * **How We Use Your Personal Data.** We use the information (including Personal Data) we collect and/or receive mainly to administer and provide the Services, contact you with administrative information, contact you with marketing offers (if you indicate your desire to receive them), and improve the Services. 
  * **Basis for Processing Your Personal Data.** Processing your Personal Data is necessary for the performance of the Terms and the provision of the Services to you. Processing for the purposes of developing new and enhancing our products and Services, for the marketing of our products and services, for analytics and usage analysis, for fraud prevention and for security and for our recordkeeping, protection of our legal rights, and complying with our legal obligations – are all necessary for the purposes of legitimate interests that we pursue. 
  * **Sharing the Personal Data We Collect.** We share the Personal Data we collect with our service providers and subcontractors who assist us in the operation of the Services and process the information on our behalf and under our instructions, as well as with our business partners and affiliates who may offer you products and services, based on your preferences (if you indicate your desire to receive these). When we act as a processor on behalf of the Third Party App Developers, we will share your Personal Data with the applicable Third Party App Developers. 
  * **International Transfer.** We use service providers and/or subcontractors and/or cooperate with or have business partners and affiliates located in countries other than your own, and send them your Personal Data. We will ensure that we have agreements in place with such parties that ensure the same level of privacy and data protection as set forth in this Privacy Notice. You hereby consent to such international transfer. 
  * **Security.** We implement industry standard measures aimed at reducing the risks of damage and unauthorized access or use of Personal Data, but they do not provide absolute information security. Such measures include physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards (such as secure servers, firewalls, antivirus and SSL encryption), access control, and other internal security policies. 
  * **Your Rights.** Subject to applicable law and additional rights as set forth below, you may have a right to access, update and/or delete your Personal Data and obtain a copy of the Personal Data we have collected about you. You can change your mind at any time about your election to receive marketing communications from us and/or having your Personal Data processed for direct marketing purposes. You also have the right to object at any time to processing your personal data for certain purposes, including marketing purposes. 
  * **Data Retention.** We retain information for as long as necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Notice. To determine the appropriate retention period, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the Personal Data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your Personal Data, the purposes for which we process your Personal Data and whether those purposes can be achieved through other means, as well as applicable legal requirements. 
  * **Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies.** We use cookies and similar technologies to help personalize your experience by helping save your settings and customizations across visits and providing you targeted content and advertisements matching your interests, which we have identified based on your activity and browsing history on the Services. 
  * **Children.** We do not knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children under the age of eighteen (18). In the event that you become aware that an individual under the age of eighteen (18) has enrolled without parental permission, please advise us immediately. 
  * **Third-Party Applications and Services.** All use of third-party applications (including the Third Party Apps) or services is at your own risk and subject to such third party's privacy policies. 
  * **Communications.** Subject to your consent and applicable law, we may send you e-mail or other messages about us or our Services. You can stop receiving future communications from us by following the UNSUBSCRIBE link located at the bottom of each communication, by emailing us at [support@overwolf.com](mailto:support@overwolf.com) or through your account settings. 
  * **Changes to the Privacy Notice.** We may change this Privacy Notice from time and shall notify you of material changes. 
  * **Comments and Questions.** If you have any comments or questions about this privacy notice, or if you wish to exercise your legal rights with respect to your Personal Data, please contact us at [support@overwolf.com](mailto:support@overwolf.com).

#### Data we collect

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect information from you, as further described below: 

## Personal Data

When you use our Services you may provide us some Personal Data such as, but not limited to, email address, username, profile picture, billing information, etc. We collect some of this data when you download our client and some when you register for the Services. Please note that if different users use one downloaded client, we view the consent provided and/or notification made of how we process Personal Data when the client is downloaded to apply to all the different users of such client. Please do not use such client unless you agree to the terms of this Privacy Notice. 

We may also automatically record certain Personal Data, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. 

We may also collect Personal Data received from third parties to the extent that they have entered into an agreement with you. For example, by using the Facebook login feature. 

When you interact with us through the Services, we receive and store certain data, such as your activities within the Services (games you played, language preference, referring site, pages viewed and the order of those pages etc) and information related to the device on which our Services are running (operating system version, data about your connected devices, hardware details etc). We can receive aggregated data containing impressions, revenue, video stats, as well as confirmation of user completions. 

It is your voluntary decision whether to provide us with any such Personal Data, but if you refuse to provide such information we may not be able to register you and/or provide you with the Services. 

## How We Use Your Personal Data

We and any of our trusted third-party subcontractors and service providers use the Personal Data we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to provide you with the Services and provide a safe and enjoyable user experience; (2) providing customer support and processing your orders, requests, questions and concerns; (3) understand the usage trends and preferences of our users and services in order to maintain, analyze, develop, update, and improve our products and services; (4) to provide you with customized content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Service, on the Third-Party Apps, on other third-party sites or apps you may visit, or via e-mail, based upon your shopping history and usage of products you have previously purchased, the content on our Services you have clicked on and/or your preferences; (5) to contact you with informational newsletters and promotional materials relating to our Services; (6) to review the usage and operations of our Services; (7) to use your data in an aggregated, non-specific format for analytical purposes (as detailed below), including for monetizing purposes; (8) protect against activities that may threaten the security, integrity, or availability of our or another party's products, systems, and services and address any problems with the Services (9) to provide customer support; (10) to satisfy our legitimate interests, while at all times ensuring that your rights and freedoms are not affected and (11) maintain corporate or business records consistent with our retention policies and applicable law. 

## Aggregated Data

Aggregated data is anonymous and will not be linked to any specific individual. In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, we may conduct research on our customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the data collected. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and we may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners without restriction, under commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

## Analytics

We and/or our service providers or subcontractors, use analytics tools ("Tools"), including "Google Analytics" to collect information about the use of the Services. Such Tools collect information such as how often users visit the Services, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites and mobile applications they used prior to visiting the Services. The Tools may collect certain Personal Data, and may link such Personal Data to specific information stored in our customer database. We use the information we get from the Tools to improve our Services. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use located at [www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and the Google Privacy Policy located at [policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). 

## Legal Uses

We may use your Personal Data as required or permitted by any applicable law.

#### Basis for Processing Your Personal Data

We use your Personal Data based upon the following legal bases: (i) when necessary for legitimate interests we pursue; (ii) when necessary for the performance of the Terms and the provision of the Services to you; (iii) when you have consented to such processing, and (iv) when necessary to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation. 

The legitimate interests we pursue when processing your Personal Data include the following purposes: (i) developing and enhancing our products and Services; (ii) for analytics and usage analysis of our Services; (iii) for the marketing of our products and services; (iv) for fraud prevention and security; and (v) for our recordkeeping and protection of our legal rights. In conducting such processing activities, we balance these legitimate interests against the rights and interests of our users. If you would like more information regarding how we make such determinations, please contact us through the contact information specified below. 

Please note that we may process your Personal Data for more than one legal basis depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your Personal Data. Please contact us if you would like details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your Personal Data. 

#### Disclosure or Sharing of Data with Third Parties

We will not share Personal Data with third parties or other Overwolf users without your explicit permission or according to this Privacy Policy, except when required by law, regulation, subpoena or court order. 

## Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties

Like many businesses, we sometimes hire other companies or individuals to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include, but are not limited to email services, customer support services, hosting of databases, servers and processing payments, data warehouse for BI needs, dashboard system, databases for supporting product features, databases for real-time analytics, CDN providers, social marketing, remote support, product analytics, CRM and sales tracking for business development backend systems, website heatmaps, backend system for managing Appstore content, communications with app developers, writing and maintaining QA test cases. 

Please see the lists below for our current service providers and third party cookie providers. We try to keep these lists current and will try to update the lists promptly to reflect any changes. 

Such service providers, business partners, affiliates, and subcontractors currently include the following: 

Service name  | Used for  | Country  | Uses cookies?   
---|---|---|---  
Redshift  | Data warehouse for BI needs  | United States and others  | No   
Redash  | Dashboard system for Redshift  | Israel  | No   
Google Analytics  | Product analytics for BI needs  | United States  | Yes   
Couchbase  | Database for supporting product features  | United States  | No   
MySQL  | Database for supporting product features  | United States  | No   
Redis  | Database for supporting product features  | United States  | No   
Graphite  | Database for real-time analytics  | United States  | No   
Grafana  | Dashboard system for Graphite database  | United States  | No   
MongoDB  | Database for supporting product features  | United States  | No   
DynamoDB  | Database for supporting product features  | United States, Ireland  | No   
Highwinds  | CDN provider  | United States  | No   
Akamai  | CDN provider  | United States and others  | No   
Cloudfront  | CDN / Web hosting  | United States, Ireland  | No   
Gmail  | Internal and external company communication  | United States  | Yes   
Freshdesk  | Customer support management  | United States  | Yes   
Twitter  | Social marketing, Customer support  | United States  | Yes   
Facebook  | Social marketing, Customer support  | United States  | Yes   
TeamViewer  | A solution for providing remote support to customers  | Germany  | No   
Discord  | Internal company communication, Customer support  | United States  | Yes   
HippoVideo  | Create, share, and publish training videos for knowledge bases etc.  | United States  | Yes   
Yandex  | Product analytics for BI needs  | Russia  | Yes   
Fabric  | Database and Product analytics for BI needs  | United States  | Yes   
Base  | CRM and sales tracking for business development  | United States  | No   
Flow  | Task and project management, CRM for business development  | Canada  | No   
Slack  | Internal company communication, communication with 3rd party developers  | United States  | Yes   
Mail Chimp  | Marketing email distribution  | United States  | Yes   
OpenCMS  | Backend system for managing Appstore content  | Germany  | No   
Comeet  | HR Recruitment solution  | Israel  | No   
LinkedIn  | HR Recruitment solution  | United States  | No   
Glassdoor  | HR Recruitment solution  | United States  | No   
TestRails  | Writing and maintaining QA test cases  | Germany  | No   
Youtrack  | Bugs and project management tool  | Czech Republic  | No   
HotJar  | Website Heatmaps and analytics  | Malta  | Yes   
PayPal  | Payment Services provision  |  |   
  
Advertising - Demand partners (who supply us with bids for ads) and related service providers 

Name  | Used for  | Country  | Uses cookies?   
---|---|---|---  
Appnexus (AT&T)  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Oath (Verizon Communications)  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
PubMatic  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Telaria  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Openx  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Twitch Interactive  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
SpotX (RTL Group)  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
RhythmOne  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Exponential Interactive  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
LKQD  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Improve Digital  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | Netherlands  | Yes   
PulsePoint  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
33Across  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Smartclip (RTL Group)  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | Germany  | Yes   
Smartclip Mexico (RTL Group)  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | Mexico  | Yes   
IndexExchange  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Unruly  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United Kingdom  | Yes   
PCGamesN  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United Kingdom  | Yes   
Video Now  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | Russia  | Yes   
LoopMe  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United Kingdom  | Yes   
Playwire Media  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Iron Source  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | Israel  | Yes   
Aniview  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United States  | Yes   
Enthusiast Gaming  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | Canada  | Yes   
Whenever Media  | Advertising / Demand Partner  | United Kingdom  | Yes   
  
Advertising related service providers

Name  | Used for  | Country  | Uses cookies?   
---|---|---|---  
Google Ad Manager  | Ad servers  | United States  | Yes   
Aniview  | Ad servers  | Israel  | Yes   
IronSource  | Ad servers  | Israel  | Yes   
Protected Media  | Ad fraud solution  | Israel  | Yes   
Pixalate  | Ad fraud solution  | United States  | Yes   
  
Additionally, when you have consented to such disclosure, we may provide to you targeted offers and advertising on both our Services, as well as on other apps/platform/sites you choose to visit, based upon your purchase history and usage of products you have previously purchased/the content on our Services you have clicked on and/or on your preferences. 

## Third Party App Developers

Third Party App Developers using our SDK or API will have access to their end users' data, including, but not limited to game data, device information, connected hardware, played games, captured media, etc. We required the Third Party App Developers to use such data only to provide the SDK/API functionality within their applications and/or services. 

## Joint Venture Partners

We may collaborate with another company or individual for the purposes of jointly promoting and improving our products and services, or their products and services. With your consent, we may disclose your Personal Data to them for these purposes. These joint venture marketing partners may also contact you regarding other products, services and promotions. We will only disclose your information under a dedicated Data Processing Addendum signed by all parties to ensure adequate protection of your data and privacy. 

## Aggregated or Non-identifiable Data

We may also share aggregated or non-personally identifiable information with our partners or others for business purposes. 

## Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Data as set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

## Legal Requirement

We may disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, regulation, subpoena, court order or other law enforcement obligations (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company or Related Companies, (iii) to protect the rights, property or safety of third parties (iv) protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (v) protect against legal liability. 

#### Unsolicited information

If you choose to post information on any of our online venues such as our Forums, Blogs, Social media pages, the Overwolf Appstore, etc. please remember that any information disclosed in these venues may be automatically made public, and by posting it you provide your consent to its disclosure. You should exercise caution when disclosing any information (including Personal Data) in such venues, as you do not know who will access or use such information and for what purposes. 

#### International Transfer

We use subcontractors and service providers and have business partners and affiliates who are located in countries other than your own, as set forth above and send them information we receive (including Personal Data). We conduct such international transfers since we use trusted service providers located in different countries. We will ensure that these third parties will be subject to written agreements ensuring the same level of privacy and data protection as set forth in this Privacy Notice, including appropriate remedies in the event of the violation of your data protection rights in such third country. 

Whenever we transfer your Personal Data to third parties based outside of the European Economic Area (EEA), we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented: 

  * We will only transfer your Personal Data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for Personal Data by the European Commission. 
  * Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give Personal Data the same protection it has in the EEA. 
  * Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they have been certified by the EU-US Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to Personal Data shared between the Europe and the US or any other arrangement which has been approved by the European Commission.

Please contact us the contact information listed below if you would like further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your Personal Data out of the EEA. 

You hereby consent to such international transfer described above. 

#### Security

We make efforts to follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Data submitted to and collected by us, both during transmission and once we receive it, including by implementing the below: 

**Safeguards** \- The physical, electronic, and procedural safeguard we employ to protect your data include secure servers, firewalls and SSL encryption of data. 

**Access Control** \- We dedicate efforts for a proper management of system entries and limit access only to authorized personnel on a need to know basis of least privilege rules, regularly review permissions and revoke access immediately after employee termination. 

**Internal Policies** \- We maintain and regularly review and update our privacy related and information security policies. 

**Personnel** \- We require new employees to sign non-disclosure agreements according to applicable law and industry customary practice. 

**Encryption** \- We encrypt the data in transit using secure SSL protocols. 

**Database Backup** – Our databases are backed up on a periodic basis for certain data and which are verified regularly. Backups are encrypted and stored within the production environment to preserve their confidentiality and integrity and are tested regularly to ensure availability, and are accessed only by authorized personnel. 

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

#### Your Rights - How to Access and Limit Our Use of Certain Information

You have certain rights in relation to the Personal Data that we hold about you, as detailed below. We reserve the right to ask for reasonable evidence to verify your identity before we provide you with any information and/or comply with any of your requests, as detailed below: 

  * **Right of Access and Data Portability.** You have a right to know what Personal Data we collect about you and, in some cases, to have the information communicated to you. Subject to the limitations in applicable law, you may be entitled to obtain from us a copy of the Personal Data you provided to us (excluding information that we obtained from other sources) in a structured, commonly-used, and machine-readable format, and you may have the right to (request that we) transmit such Personal Data to another party. If you wish to exercise this right please contact us letting us know what information in particular you would like to receive and/or transmit. Subject to applicable law, we may charge you with a fee. Please note that we may not be able to provide you with all the information you request, for instance, if the information includes Personal Data about another person. Where we are not able to provide you with information that you have asked for, we will endeavor to explain to you why. We will try to respond to any request for a right of access as soon as possible. 
  * **Right to Correct Personal Data.** Subject to the limitations in applicable law, you may request that we update, correct or delete inaccurate or outdated Personal Data and/or that we suspend the use of Personal Data, the accuracy of which you may contest, while we verify the status of that Personal Data. We will correct your Personal Data within a reasonable time from the receipt of your written request thereof. 
  * **Deletion of Personal Data ("Right to Be Forgotten").** In certain circumstances you have a right to have Personal Data that we hold about you deleted. Should you wish to have any Personal Data about you deleted, please contact us, using the contact information specified in this Privacy Notice. Subject to applicable law, we will delete Personal Data provided to us by a user within a reasonable time from the receipt of a written (including via email) request by such user to delete such collected Personal Data. We cannot restore information once it has been deleted. Please note that to ensure that we do not collect any further Personal Data, you should terminate your account with us and clear our cookies from any device where you have used our Services. We may retain certain Personal Data (including following your request to delete) for audit and record-keeping purposes, as well as other purposes, all as permissible and/or required under applicable law. We may also retain your information in an anonymized form. 
  * **Account Deactivation.** You can ask us to deactivate your account by contacting us using the information below. In order to deactivate your account, we may ask you for additional information. 
  * **Right to Restrict Processing.** You may request at any time that we limit the processing of your Personal Data if you believe that either: (i) the Personal Data is inaccurate and wish us to limit processing until we verify its accuracy; (ii) the processing is unlawful, but you do not wish us to erase the Personal Data; (iii) we no longer need the Personal Data for the purposes for which it was collected, but you still need it for the establishment, exercise, or defense of a legal claim; (iv) you have exercised your Right to Object (below) and we are in the process of verifying our legitimate grounds for processing. We may continue to use your Personal Data after a restriction request either: (a) with your consent; (b) for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; or (iii) to protect the rights of another natural or legal person. 
  * **Direct Marketing Opt Out.** You can change your mind at any time about your election to receive marketing communications from us and/or having your Personal Data processed for direct marketing purposes. If you do, please notify us by contacting us as detailed in this Privacy Notice. We will process your request as soon as reasonably possible, however it may take a few days for us to update our records before any opt out is effective. 
  * **Right to Object.** Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to object to processing of your Personal Data including for the purpose of direct marketing. 
  * **Withdrawal of Consent.** You may withdraw your consent in connection with any processing of your Personal Data based on a previously granted consent. 
  * **Supervisory Authority.** If you are a European Citizen, you may have the right to submit a complaint to the relevant supervisory data protection authority.

#### Data Retention

Subject to applicable law, we retain information as necessary for the purposes set forth above. We may delete information from our systems, without notice to you, once we deem it is no longer necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Notice. We may also retain your information in an anonymized form. In addition, retention by any of our processors may vary, in accordance with the processor's retention policy. 

To determine the appropriate retention period, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the Personal Data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your Personal Data, the purposes for which we process your Personal Data and whether those purposes can be achieved through other means, as well as applicable legal requirements. 

Please contact us through the contact information listed below if you would like details regarding the retention periods for different types of your Personal Data. 

#### Online links to other sites

Overwolf and Overwolf members or users can link to other websites of third-parties that provide useful information/services, or who have agreed to offer goods and services to Overwolf members (For example YouTube, Twitter, Google etc.). Any Personal Data you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to this third-party and is subject to that third-party's provider's privacy policy, except as described above. Overwolf is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of Web sites to which we link. Links from our site to third-parties or other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of each web site before providing them with Personal Data. To sum up - we cannot be held responsible for any third-party Web sites and accessing their content will be subject to their own privacy policies, which again - we advise you to check. 

#### Children

Overwolf does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 18, and you must be 18 years of age or older in order to install and use Overwolf. Parents are able to install Overwolf for and/or set up Overwolf accounts for their children. In this way verifiable parental consent is required in order to register a child under the age of 18 to be enrolled to Overwolf product and services, and any parent setting up an account for his or her child hereby represents and warrants that he or she is the parent or legal guardian of such child, and has the authority to provide information and render consents on behalf of such child. In the event you become aware that an individual under the age of 18 has enrolled without parental permission, please advise us immediately. 

#### Communications

Subject to your consent and applicable law, we may send you e-mail or other messages and/or a newsletter about us or our Services. You will be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial messages and stop receiving future communication from us by following the UNSUBSCRIBE link in any such email or message, by emailing us at [support@overwolf.com](mailto:support@overwolf.com), as well as through your account settings. Please note that we reserve the right to send you service-related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages relating to your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Should you not wish to receive such communications you may cancel your account. 

#### Updates to this privacy policy

When visiting the Services, you shall be asked to accept the terms of this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree with the terms hereof, please do not use the Services. Overwolf may update this Privacy Policy from time to time - we encourage you to review it periodically. We will notify you of material changes.We will post the updated Privacy Notice on this page. Please come back to this page every now and then to make sure you are familiar with the latest version. Any new Privacy Notice will be effective from the date it is accepted by you. 

#### Comments and Questions

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy please [contact us](http://www.overwolf.com/contact). 

_Last updated: November 2018_

### Cookies

#### Cookies Policy

## What are Cookies?

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to a user's browser, desktop client or device. The browser provides this piece of text to the device of the originating user when this visitor returns.

  * A "session cookie" is temporary and will remain on your device until you leave the Services.
  * A "persistent" cookie may be used to help save your settings and customizations across visits. It will remain on your device for much longer or until you delete it.
  * First-party cookies are placed by us, while third-party cookies may be placed by a third party. We use both first- and third-party cookies.
  * Information may also be collected through web beacons, which are small graphic images ("pixel tags"), which usually work together with cookies in order to identify users and user behavior. These may be shared with third parties.

We may use the terms "cookies" to refer to all technologies that we may use to store data in your browser or device or that collect information or help us identify you in the manner described above.

## How We Use Cookies

We use cookies and similar technologies for a number of reasons, for example, in order to (i) help personalize your experience by helping save your settings and customizations across visits and provide you with targeted content matching your interests, which we have identified based on your activity and viewing history on our Services and (ii) to help serve you ads relevant to your interests, which we have identified based on your activity and viewing history on our Services or your purchase history and usage of products and services you have previously purchased. 

We use cookies and similar technologies to help personalize your experience and to personalize the ads we serve you. Third parties through which we provide the Services and/or our business partners may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, as well as on our desktop client, or using web beacons to collect information in the course of advertising being served on different websites and on our desktop client. When visiting these Services, you shall be asked to accept the terms of this Privacy Notice, including the use of and placement of cookies and other similar technologies on your device as specified herein. For additional info about cookies and how to block them you may check this site [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

The specific names and types of the cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies we use may change from time to time. However, the cookies we use generally fall into one of the following categories: 

Type of Cookie  | Why We Use These Cookies   
---|---  
Necessary  | These cookies are necessary in order to allow the Services to work correctly. They enable you to access the Services, move around, and access different services, features, and tools. Examples include remembering previous actions (e.g. entered text) when navigating back to a page in the same session. These cookies cannot be disabled.   
Functionality  | These cookies remember your settings and preferences and the choices you make (such as language or regional preferences) in order to help us personalize your experience and offer you enhanced functionality and content.   
Security  | These cookies can help us identify and prevent security risks. They may be used to store your session information to prevent others from changing your password without your login information.   
Performance  | These cookies can help us collect information to help us understand how you use our Services, such as whether you have viewed messages or specific pages and how long you spent on each page. This helps us improve the performance of our Services.   
Analytics  | These cookies collect information regarding your activity on our Services to help us learn more about which features are popular with our users and how our Services can be improved.   
Advertising  | These cookies are placed in order to deliver content, including ads relevant and meaningful to you and your interests. They may also be used to deliver targeted advertising or to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. This can help us track how efficient advertising campaigns are, both for our own Services and for other websites. Such cookies may track your browsing habits and activity when visiting both our Services and those of third-parties.   
  
#### How to Adjust Your Preferences

You are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. Please note that some features of the Services may function improperly when cookies are disabled or removed. 

Overwolf's unique technology called "Cookie Sync" creates copies of the cookies that are available on your default browser and stores them on the Overwolf desktop client. These cookies are copied "as is", and are identical to the original cookies that are stored on your default browser; however they may change over time on the desktop client.   
Overwolf uses "Cookie Sync" in order to properly operate the Products and Services, relay analytic information, improve the user experience and personalize ads that are displayed within the Services. 

We assume you accept the use of these cookies, as you already gave your consent to using these cookies for targeted ads on your default browser. 

Our Services have implemented Google Analytics Display Advertising features including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Using the Ads Settings, visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize [Google Display Network ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site. Our Services uses data aggregated from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as interests) for general reporting and improvement of our Services, and possibly for ad remarketing lists. 

If you prefer generalised (non-personalised, non-targeted) ads, visit the links below to opt-out of cookies from major third party behavioral advertising providers (Please note that this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads). 

  * Network Advertising Initiative: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>
  * European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance: <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>
  * <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>
  * Digital Advertising Alliance: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>
  * Google Analytics: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

For a list of First Party Cookies and a link to a list of Third Party Cookies, please see "Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties" above. 

_Last updated: August 2019_
